import "Catalog/catalog.css";


// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],

}



export var cards = {
  //#region Table de 0
  "0x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "0x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '0 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  //#endregion Table de zéro

  //#region Table de 1
  "1x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "1x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "1"
  },
  "1x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "2"
  },
  "1x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "3"
  },
  "1x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "1x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "1x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "1x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "7"
  },
  "1x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "1x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "1x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '1 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 1

  //#region Table de 2
  "2x0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "2x1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "2"
  },
  "2x2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "2x3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "2x4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "2x5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "2x6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "2x7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "14"
  },
  "2x8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "2x9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "2x10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '2 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "20"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 2

  //#region Table de 3
  "3x0": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "3x1": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "3"
  },
  "3x2": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "6"
  },
  "3x3": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "9"
  },
  "3x4": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "3x5": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "3x6": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "3x7": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "21"
  },
  "3x8": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "24"
  },
  "3x9": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "27"
  },
  "3x10": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '3 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "30"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 3

  //#region Table de 4
  "4x0": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "4x1": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "4"
  },
  "4x2": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "8"
  },
  "4x3": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "12"
  },
  "4x4": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "16"
  },
  "4x5": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "20"
  },
  "4x6": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "24"
  },
  "4x7": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "28"
  },
  "4x8": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "32"
  },
  "4x9": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "36"
  },
  "4x10": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '4 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "40"
  },
  //#endregion Table de 4

  //#region Table de 5
  "5x0": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "5x1": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "5"
  },
  "5x2": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "10"
  },
  "5x3": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "15"
  },
  "5x4": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "20"
  },
  "5x5": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "25"
  },
  "5x6": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "30"
  },
  "5x7": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "35"
  },
  "5x8": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "40"
  },
  "5x9": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "45"
  },
  "5x10": {    
    type: 'text',
    question: '5 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "50"
  },  
  //#endregion Table de 5

};